Every holiday season, millions travel safely by air.
This Christmas will be different.
Carry-On is a thriller, action film directed by Jaume Collet-Serra.
An airport security officer races to outsmart a mysterious traveler forcing
him to let a dangerous item slip onto a Christmas Eve flight.
Ethan Kopek, played by Taron Egerton.
Traveler, played by Jason Bateman.
Nora Parisi, played by Sofia Carson.
Elena Cole, played by Danielle Deadwyler.
Watcher, played by Theo Rossi.
Agent Alcott, played by Logan Marshall-Green.
Carry-On is a 2024 American action thriller film directed
by Jaume Collet-Serra and written by T.
The film stars Taron Egerton, Sofia Carson,
Danielle Deadwyler, and Jason Bateman.
Its plot follows a young TSA officer who is blackmailed into allowing a nerve agent
on board a flight, which will kill 250 people, during Christmas Eve.
Carry-On was released by Netflix on December 13, 2024, received positive reviews from critics, and
earned more views during its opening week than any other film released on Netflix in 2024.
The film explores themes of underdog, race against time,
blackmail, flight, los angeles, california.
The tone is intense.